# Paweł Kanarek

Senior Mobile Developer with over 10 years of experience in Xamarin and .NET MAUI, delivering production-ready code. As a Machine Learning enthusiast who spent the past year self-learning, I believe that I would be a great asset to your AI Engineering team.

# Experience

#### Self Employed

#### **Al Developer** Aug 2023 - Present

- Fine-tuned the Stable Diffusion XL (SDXL) model to generate animated sprites.
- Collected, prepared, and created a dataset consisting of 560 labeled images.
- Created a training script for the SDXL model in the Flax framework. See my spraix repository for more details.
- Completed *PyTorch for Deep Learning Bootcamp* course on Udemy and *Neural Networks: Zero to Hero* by Andrej Karpathy.

## Legimi

### Xamarin Developer Aug 2022 – Aug 2023

- Maintained popular Legimi application on Android, iOS, Windows, MacOS and e-Ink platforms.
- Wrote documentation, planned, estimated, and implemented new features.
- Managed multiple tasks during two-week tech support sprints, which included end-user and internal teams assistance, bug fixes, CI build coordination, and publishing applications across various platforms.
- Created automated UI, integration, and unit tests.
- Gained experience in C# functional programming using Reactive Extensions.

# Insys Video Technologies

```
Mobile Technical Leader July 2020 - July 2022

Senior Xamarin Developer Apr 2020 - July 2020

Xamarin Developer June 2016 - Apr 2020

Solar2D Game and App Developer Aug 2013 - June 2016
```

- Performed technical interviews in the hiring process.
- Created streaming applications for watching DRM-protected live streams and VODs for iOS,
   Android, AndroidTV, AppleTV, Windows Phone platforms with Xamarin and Solar2D frameworks.
- Collaborated in creating custom Framework and White Label Product, leading to dozens of successful implementations; examples include: simpliTV Android / iOS / AndroidTV, PAOK TV Android / iOS, BeActiveTV Android / iOS, INEA Online TV Android / iOS, Cineman Android / iOS, Mojeekino.pl Android / iOS, Benfica Play Android / iOS, Trwam TV Android / iOS.
- Set up infrastructure for UI and integration tests.

# **Technologies**

Listed in order of proficiency; enthusiastic about the bolded ones.

- Programming Languages: C#, Python, Kotlin, Java, Lua, GDScript, Dart, JavaScript, Objective-C, C++, C, Assembly, F#.
- Frameworks: Xamarin, MAUI, PyTorch, Jax, Flax, Flutter, ASP.NET, Godot, Solar2D.
- IDEs: **JetBrains Rider**, **VS Code**, **Visual Studio** (I also created an extension, available on the Marketplace), Android Studio, XCode.
- Other: **git**, Jenkins, GitHub, Bitbucket, **Hugging Face**, **Stable Diffusion**, Rx.NET, RealmDB, Jira, Confluence, Redmine, ExoPlayer, MVVMCross, Prism.

# Education

# Poznań University of Technology

### **B.Sc. in Automatic Control and Robotics** 2011 - 2017

• For my diploma thesis, "Weather Station on the Arduino Processor", I developed a web app in ASP.NET and created mobile apps for Android and iOS platforms, with real-time view of the results from the station.

# Languages

• Polish: Native speaker.

• English: Fluent (B2 level).